ruled.me 2019-03-31

# Privacy Policy | Ruled Me

## **Privacy Policy**

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at contact@ruled.me

At www.ruled.me, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.ruled.me and how it is used.

 **Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, www.ruled.me makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

 **Cookies and Web Beacons**  
www.ruled.me does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

 **DoubleClick DART Cookie**  
.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.ruled.me.  
.:: Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.ruled.me and other sites on the Internet.  
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – https://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include…

  *  **Google**
  *  **Amazon**
  *  **Sendowl**

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.ruled.me send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

www.ruled.me has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.ruled.me’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

* * *

##  **Disclaimer**

The information provided on this site, including text and graphics, is for informational purposes only. It is not to be construed as medical care or medical advice and is not a replacement for medical care given by physicians or trained medical personnel. ruled.me does not directly or indirectly practice medicine, nor does it dispense medical advice, diagnosis, treatment or any other medical service as part of this website.

Always seek the advice of your physician or other qualified healthcare provider(s) when experiencing symptoms or health problems, or before starting any new treatment. ruled.me is not to be held responsible for any inaccuracies, omissions, or editorial errors, or for any consequences resulting from the information provided. By continuing to view this site, visitors indicate acceptance of these terms. Visitors who do not accept these terms should not access, use, interact with or view these web pages.

Recipes and information on this site should not be used without consulting a medical professional who is experienced in the administration of the ketogenic diet. Although some recipes found on ruled.me may have been verified as “ketogenic” by qualified dietitians, they are not tailored to meet the specific nutritional requirements of all individuals. Serious harm could occur if the ketogenic diet is utilized without proper oversight from medical professionals. The ketogenic diet in any form or ratio should NEVER be started on your own without the guidance of qualified medical advice.

It is your responsibility to evaluate the information and results from the tools and information we provide. If you are a health care professional, you should exercise your professional judgment in evaluating any information, and we encourage you to confirm the information contained on our website with other sources before undertaking any treatment or action based on it. If you are a consumer, you should evaluate the information together with your physician or other qualified health care professional.
